I'll just eat the show, then I'll go away.
I'm going to go out somewhere. I'm resting, I'm resting, I'm resting, I'm resting, I'm resting, I'm resting, I'm resting, I'm resting, I'm resting...
Today we're going to explore the world of butajishis, and we're going to buy a lot of them!
We're temporarily opening an additional candy shop on the 4th floor of Ibins, and we're planning to expand and fully open it in the near future.
It's temporarily open, so I went there today.
We're all grown-ups now, so when we were little we used to calculate our allowance and buy things, but now we're adults.
But now we're adults, so let's go and buy.
Let's move on to the store.
I want to help everyone!
Here we are!
Please buy as many candy bars as you can here.
I'm so excited!
Carrots first.
What's that?
This...
I know what it is!
You don't know?
I've seen them before, but I've never had them.
I ate it all in one gulp.
Look at that Dora chocolate.
These are delicious.
There's a maple syrup flavor.
I'll buy these.
I've missed these.
It's huge.
I used to have one of these, but I'm all grown up now.
It makes my baseball team tingle.
You're enjoying it, aren't you?
I've always wanted to try it.
De mochi chocolate.
I like this one, too.
It's good, isn't it?
I'll buy all of these.
Seriously.
It crackles when you put it in your mouth.
I was so scared to eat these.
When I was little.
Iwamushi (Japanese rock beetle)
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
It stinks!
stink
Mon-chan, I love young donuts!
Then I'll get some for you, Mon-chan.
Okay.
I'll see you next time
I'll see you next time.
It's okay if you're planning a second one or something
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Souvenirs.
Oh, here they are.
A souvenir from Akarin.
What?
Here it is, here it is!
Chukyo.
Chukyo?
Congratulations!
What are you doing, Uncle Yatsu?
Uncle Yatsu?
You're totally cute!
I'm so happy!
Uncle Yatsu's favorite.
I'm used to it.
That's great.
You like it that much?
I used to live on this.
You mean you were poor.
You mean you like it too much?
I was so poor I ate this all day long.
I've never seen this before.
I've never seen you before either.
Really? - Maybe I've never seen it before.
What's it like?
It's kind of like chewing candy.
It's really delicious.
I'm curious.
You know, it's not like it's obvious that you're the one who brought it.
Don't cover up the empty space.
Don't cheat! Don't cheat by pulling over!
Hold on, hold on, hold on to your new meal!
I'm a big fan too!
Kalpas!
Japanese ones!
I got them all!
No way!
Just the bottom box.
This is from Yamagata.
Kalpas. That's right.
I love it.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Oh, yes.
Yes, it is.
Close.
I hope this is okay then, office-wise.
I grew up eating these.
It's really cute.
My parents didn't serve us dinner.
That's why I ate this.
What's this?
Candy.candy
Nyonya Nyonya!
It's okay to say it.
It's not like it's forbidden.
It's just that you can't say "no" to these characters...
Millet dumplings.
Nyanya Nyanya!
I heard it grows!
Wow.
You like it this much?
I really like it.
If the boys didn't say anything about it...
Girls will eat it.
I'm too popular to talk to them.
Sorry.
Ha-ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Here, I'll buy this.
How much is it?
How much? Let's guess.
Let's guess.
Buy this much.
Total? Or just one?
Why don't we just go with the total?
4,000 yen.
One hundred yen.
4,100 yen.
5,800 yen.
No, I don't think so.
3,800 yen is fine
10 yen and so on
Products that are not even close to 100 yen
Even if you collect them all
3,800 yen
4,900 yen
A crow ran by.
That's great.
I bought 8,000 yen worth of candy.
For real?
That's terrible.
Thank you very much.
Isn't it bad?
Oh, no!
I'm back.
I'm back! How much was it?
Hama-chan's good... 8,075 yen.
Look at this long-throated receipt. It's like a scroll... If a kid saw it now, he'd cry.
They'll think it's scary. They won't want to hear it.
So please tell me it's an "18" video.
What's wrong with that?
I'll start with my favorite.
Okay, we'll eat this one first.
Hey, then, from the looks of it.
That's right.
It's so cute!
Can I try this one? I remember your mouth.
I got it, I got it, I got it!
This is good!
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Okay, let's eat.
Oh, what was that?
This is a candy that I love
I bought a box of them.
I bought a box.
Bon appétit.
Yes, it's delicious!
The usual taste.
Do you have a story about your first encounter with Chukan? First encounter?
No, I've been eating it since I was very young. When I went to Nagai Ichiya with my sister for the first time in a long time, we talked about how much we missed it, and when we tried it, it was perfect for my taste buds.
I thought it was so good, I was devastated. That's how we met.
How are you feeling now? I'm in a relationship. Are you planning to get married?
Don't eat your food so fast. Are you putting your marriage on the line? You just said that and ate something, didn't you? Now.
Tell me what you just ate. Crackle, crackle, panic. Do you hear that?
I hear you.
Can I tell you the best part of this?
Go ahead.
Most of these come in packs of five.
But this one has six.
So every time you finish one, there's still one in the bag.
I see. It's like a bargain.
I always feel happy when I eat these.
That's what I'm talking about now.
I see. It's good to eat them, isn't it?
And Mr. Fujita, you just had kalpas.
What?
Tell me the next time you go there.
Yes, this is how I eat.
I'm sure you'll love it.
I really love it.
I could eat this forever.
I can eat them forever.
When you were little, was there a candy store in your neighborhood?
We didn't have any. We didn't even have convenience stores.
Did we?
Is this a scary story?
In a way, it's a scary story, isn't it?
Chocolate, of course.Mochi Chocolate.
This has been around for quite a while.
Yes, it has.
Bon appétit!
Next snack.
In your generation, when you went on field trips, what kind of snack did you bring?
We used to bring snacks like "Dumplings" and "Chair snacks".
And the snacks had to be under 500 yen? It was 500 yen or less.
It was 250 yen.
That's half price.
They said no more than 250 yen? Field trip snacks.
We chopped carrots, too.
It's more about quantity than quality. That's exactly what it's like with candy. That's right. Isn't it usually 300 yen?
Yes, we chop them. We decided on 220 yen. That's too much.
Next, I'll eat this. Cotton candy. Fuku-san eats a lot of this.
He likes it. It's falling down so hard. It's not falling. I lied just now.
I'm sorry. It's down. You left it there, didn't you? Yes, it's here.
It's delicious.
You were talking about the candy store earlier. There was one near the elementary school. It was a local kind of shop, run by a neighborhood grandmother.
There was a store that sold sweets. Usually, you were not allowed to stop by there during athletic meets or other events.
So we all went there to buy sweets for field day and other events. Ah, you get excited on such occasions. I understand.
I understand.
The lady at the candy store, when she gave back the change, would she say, "Yes, 300,000 yen" when the change was only 30 yen? Oh, I might have said that. I miss it...she might have said 1,000,000 yen for 100 yen. I miss it.
How did you react? Like, "I don't like it! Like that. Simple. Good boy! Good boy!
Don't be serious. It's not "wakuman. That's the worst. It's not that. Triangular lottery chocolates.
It seems like it's been around forever.
Really? I've never seen this before.
What is it? What kind of lottery?
What kind of lottery is it?
It says "Open, fail. There's chocolate in it, isn't there? It's a lottery. What's the lottery? This.
It says "Hazure" on it. Does that mean it's a lottery? I think it means it's chocolate in the shape of a triangular lottery.
What happens if I win? You get another one. So you're saying this one is a winner or a loser?
I see.
Then let's move on. I'm too much of a slacker. Sloppy.
It's no good. It's no good.
That's right. Oh no, I've grown up. Don't get excited just because you win or lose 10 yen. Little kids.
I've grown up. Is this the end?
It's not the end, is it? I'm not finished.
I'm really done. You all know what this is.
It's a grape, just like it says. This is famous.
Pretend it's not sour? Pretend it's not sour.
And then guess who is the sour one. Have you ever pretended to be sour? Yes, I have. But it became chaotic, so we stopped.
Who was it? Everyone did it at once. It's hard to tell, that's for sure.
It became chaotic, so it was easier to understand if we just put up with it. Then, let's play rock-paper-scissors for the first time.
Me too? What? There are three of them, right?
If they're all wrong, we'll just have to eat them.
First, let's play "goo" rock-paper-scissors.
It's Aiko, right?
I'll choose Amiyu first.
First, goo-janken poke, Aiko, right?
All right.
Okay, I'll start with Amiyu.
Ready?
Okay.
Yup.
Yup. - Yup.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Not tiny at all.
Not at all.
It's just rubber.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Tastes good as usual.
Normal. Tasty.
Tasty.
También.
Which one do you like better, también?
What are you?
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm scared.
What?
Seriously?
One out of three is super sour.
Very sour.
Me too.
Young man...
Because of the interview.
What? It's sour.
It was me, for sure.
It's so sour.
I'm so sour, I had to hold it in.
What? What's this?
It was really sour.
It was so sour.
Can I have a soybean flour stick, my favorite?
I like perishables. Can I have some perishables?
There's five of them?
How many are in there? 45 of them.
Where are the hits on these?
The tip of the toothpick is red.
Ready?
Did I hit it?
What's with your "it hit me" reaction?
But it's delicious.
It's delicious, isn't it?It's good, isn't it?
Yeah, it's good. It's good, hinako.
The more you chew, the better it tastes.
It's good.
I got you some souvenirs.
I got a bunch of young doughnuts.
Everybody's getting them.
I got dinner.
You like Young Doughnuts, Hinano-san?
I love them. Hinano-san, who's on her second recording.
Yes, ma'am.
This is so unexpected.
A member gave it to me...
I got a box at my birthday.
You love them? They're delicious, aren't they?
Yeah. They have chocolate flavor.
Oh, it's good. It's good.
I don't know if I like it or not.
Whoever guessed it...
So I guess you're the winner.
Yes, sir.
Oh, it's pretty hard to swallow.
Is it in there? It's a real hit.
It's really in there.
This is so much better than Tee's.
It's a mouthful.
I've never heard of such a thing.
I've never heard of such a food reportage.
I think they're doing it now.
Five hits.
Wow!
This is really bad.
Since when did this video become about exposing the darkness?
It has become.
I've eaten 18 now.
Oh, you mean you've already eaten more than a third of them?
Well, I'm about to...
Nineteen.
Why...
Mmmm...
It's like you've hit it and missed it.
It's true.
I've had 20 sticks now.
I'm eating 24 kinako sticks right now.
And since there's no hit yet...
There's 21 left, and I've got 5 in the bag.
It's like we're the losers.
I'm on my 25th stick, 26th stick.
Hang in there, guys! Don't lose!
Messiah.
Messiah Hinano!
You've got a shot here.
Missed!
What happens when I give it to you?
The tip is red.
You made me do it?
Twenty-six now!
Yes, second one.
Missed?
What?
Nishijima result?
How is this possible?
I'm scared, scared, scared!
But anyway...
I want to prove it by eating all of them.
Let's go.
What if it's not in there?
This video will be filled with okra.
What if I want to call Nishijima Results?
Leave it to a real YouTuber.
That's not what I'm planning on doing.
There's a theory that this is a gaffe.
Maybe I'm wrong about the concept of winning.
Let's check it out.
Let's do a little Googling.
Let's Google it once
Nishijima, you're right.
Really?
Someone's looking into it.
It's so red.
Calculate the probability...
1 in 5... that's a pretty good chance.
Twenty-eight right now.
I've got goosebumps.
It's like the person who hit it is screwed.
It's like we're all doomed.
Yes, it is.
But I want to prove it anyway.
I want to keep the last five.
It's a hit.
It's a Russian flour stick.
You're right.
Ready?
Hurrrrrrrrrrrrr!
Squeeze!
squeeze~~~
Idol
Oh, but there it is!
Yes, there is!
No, of course you do!No, of course not!
Thank God!
Twenty-nine!
I finally found it!
It's right around the corner!
That's not much of a chute!
We've worked so hard to get this far!
Shall I eat all of them at once?
No, no, no, no, no.
Switch them out!
The one that's not stuck.
Okay.
One replacement.
Oh, you're making it from here already?
Oh, no, it's still...
No, it's not...
It's not coming out at all!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
You're not getting any!
This is your 30th bottle, right?
That's right.
Then I'd like to guess here.
Yeah. - Yeah.
That's right.
Okay.
Let's try this one... it's kind of beautiful.
It's beautiful.
I think we're done here.
Not at all.
Then I'll carry everyone's feelings on my shoulders.
Please.
I can do it.
If we win this, it'll be like the World Cup.
That's right.
I'll go!
Bravo!
Wow!
Woooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!
Double time cop
Compound time, compound place, pc and lee...
I've got a root canal on me.
Okay, well, I bought and ate a bunch of candy today.
How was it?
It's so much fun!
I used to dream about candy bars when I was a kid.
And now it's all come true.
I feel like I've grown up.
I'm so glad you took this video.
I felt so happy after I bought this
I have a dream
I want to teach my kids!
Something about how your dreams when you're a little kid can come true when you're an adult.
on the subject of this.
I learned it from a candy bar!
Yes, I'd like to say that.
Also, I bought this candy today.
I'll let you two take it home with you.
You can live a while with this.
Wait a minute.
You've lost a meal.
Why?
So this time we're on the fourth floor.
It's temporarily open right now.
I went to the candy store ZO, which is temporarily open right now, and bought a bunch of stuff.
It looks like it will be open in a little while.
Please come and visit us and have a blast!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much for the food!
Bye bye!
Next time